<Vertical id="interdisciplinary_activities" launchable="true">
  <!-- Opening screen -->
  <Markdown id="interdisciplinary_orientation">
## Welcome to the Interdisciplinary Studies Module

In this simulated internship at Community 360, you'll apply interdisciplinary analysis to understand the complex issue of high school dropout rates in the community.

Working with supervisor Lianne Park and your intern teammates, you'll investigate causes, review research from multiple disciplines, and develop evidence-based recommendations.
  </Markdown>
  <!-- GSU professor image -->
  <Image id="interdisciplinary_gsu_prof_image" src="images/GSU_prof.png" alt="Professor at Georgia State University" />

  <!-- Library of readings navigator -->
  <Vertical id="interdisciplinary_library">
    <Markdown id="library_intro">
## Library of Readings

Browse the research studies and resources relevant to understanding high school dropout. Click on each item to read the full text.
    </Markdown>

    <Navigator id="interdisciplinary_library_navigator"
               title="Available Readings"
               preview="DefaultPreview"
               detail="ReadingDetail">
- id: adhd_study
  name: Is ADHD a Risk Factor for High School Dropout?
  subtitle: Fried et al. (2016) - Psychology
  description: Examines ADHD as a risk factor for grade retention and dropout, controlling for IQ and learning disorders.
  ref: reading_adhd_study

- id: employment_study
  name: Is Adolescent Employment Still a Risk Factor for Dropout?
  subtitle: Staff et al. (2019) - Sociology/Economics
  description: Examines whether intensive work during high school increases dropout risk using 2009 longitudinal data.
  ref: reading_employment_study

- id: rural_urban_study
  name: Rural and Urban High School Dropout Rates
  subtitle: Jordan et al. (2012) - Education
  description: Compares dropout rates in rural vs urban areas, examining geographic and family factors.
  ref: reading_rural_urban_study

- id: marijuana_study
  name: Marijuana Use and High School Dropout
  subtitle: McCaffrey et al. (2010) - Health Economics
  description: Examines the relationship between marijuana use and dropout using propensity score methods.
  ref: reading_marijuana_study

- id: silent_epidemic
  name: The Silent Epidemic - Student Perspectives
  subtitle: Gates Foundation (2006) - Primary Source
  description: Focus group data and student survey providing direct perspectives from high school dropouts.
  ref: reading_silent_epidemic

- id: policy_brief
  name: Urgent Focus on High School Dropout Rates
  subtitle: Policy Brief - Education Policy
  description: Executive summary highlighting national dropout crisis and recommendations for intervention.
  ref: reading_policy_brief
    </Navigator>
  </Vertical>

  <!-- Team directory navigator -->
  <Vertical id="interdisciplinary_team_members">
    <Markdown id="team_directory_intro">
## Comm360 Team Directory

Explore the team directory to learn about your colleagues for this project. Click on each person to see their role, experience, and skills.
    </Markdown>

    <Navigator id="interdisciplinary_team_navigator"
               title="Comm360 Team"
               preview="TeamPreview"
               detail="TeamDetail">
- id: ty
  name: Ty
  role: Intern Teammate
  photo: /sba/images/ty.png
  bio: Intern at Comm360 focusing on program evaluation and data analysis.
  experience: 6 months at Comm360
  skills: [Data Analysis, Research, Program Evaluation]

- id: peggy
  name: Peggy
  role: Intern Teammate
  photo: /sba/images/peggy.png
  bio: Intern specializing in community outreach and stakeholder engagement.
  experience: 4 months at Comm360
  skills: [Community Outreach, Communication, Project Management]

- id: lacy
  name: Lacy
  role: Intern Teammate
  photo: /sba/images/lacy.png
  bio: Intern with focus on program development and implementation strategies.
  experience: 5 months at Comm360
  skills: [Program Development, Strategic Planning, Implementation]

- id: lianne
  name: Lianne Park
  role: Supervisor/Mentor
  photo: /sba/images/lianne.png
  bio: Director of multiple programs at Comm360 with extensive experience in program evaluation and development. Presents findings to the PDE committee.
  experience: 5 years at Comm360
  skills: [Program Management, Leadership, Strategic Planning, Evaluation]

- id: anne
  name: Anne Hastings
  role: Chief Executive Officer
  photo: /sba/images/anne.png
  bio: CEO of Comm360, making ultimate decisions about programs and resources. Reports to the board of directors.
  experience: 8 years at Comm360, 15+ years leadership experience
  skills: [Executive Leadership, Strategic Decision Making, Resource Management, Organizational Development]
    </Navigator>
  </Vertical>

</Vertical>
